So Rethunwa
[laughs]
Lal ho
Juna ke liye, let's go from here, live in the canal,
earn money from the canal, don't do that, I won't leave you, I won't go like this, I will hit you,
see, go to the canal, if I don't go anywhere, if I go, then
earn money and send it,
from where will you send the money, you are my brother, if my
brother doesn't give me money, then find the money from me,
father, brother, take care of my sister,
take her every month,
see, sister has milk, you are a scoundrel, will you take her away, you are a
scoundrel of a father, take me away, take my
sister in the
name of your father, hold me half and [ __ ] me, don't shoot with a stick, shoot and
kill me, see, Kariya jaana,
open the kitchen quietly,
sit down, sister, wash your face, wash the muva, wash the raava,
distribute it, mother-in-law, mother-in-law,
where is sister, I am busy in prayers, the old man is
over, my days are over with this mother-in-law, you can kill me, you can
kill me by poisoning, you can
kill me by hanging, you can burn me  Do you want to beat me only then will there be
happiness and peace in my life?
Yes Didi, you are right, as long as the
old man is alive, until we live happily and peacefully, if we do
n't let our sister live,
then make a plan and kill him. Didi, see, quickly go and loot the mother's son said, if you want to loot further, then go and fill the loot deeply. Didi, then say something to Bachi. Didi, refuse, first send me out, then it will be easier for me to work.
See, send me out after
beating me.
Yes, Chotki, you are right. Even if Dhana
sends me out after beating me, you will get
this done. So, make a plan,
send me out for an hour. [laughs] I will take this Bhama,
when I am out, come on, Didi, till
today the old lady has done the puja, have you come back?
Om Bhur Bhurva Swaha Tatsaviturvem Bhargo Devasya Dhimahi Dhiyo Yo
Na Prachodayat
Om Bhur Bhurva Swaha Tatsaviturvem
Bhargo Devasya
Slowly, Didi, the old
lady is still praying,
see, isn't this the case? This old lady prayed one day and died,
look, tell me, this old lady, if you had given me juice, I would have cooked it
myself, the old
lady would have died of hunger, I
thought, Didi, go and beat the old lady, my
heart is pining from within,
Om Jai Laxmi
Mata, I do
n't know anything, you
give me happiness in the sorrows of my sons, you
give me happiness in the sorrows of my sons [laughs] You ask,
Om Jai Laxmi Mata,
Om Jai Laxmi Mata
Maiya, Jai Laxmi [voice of singing]
Mata,
see Didi, how mother-in-law, if you sing the aarti, you have found
happiness in my sorrow, you find
happiness in your heart, please do
n't kill me, please, please, I do
n't give you one, I will give it to you, Didi, I will not give it to you,
Jai Mata Lakshmi, Jai Ganesh Bhagwan, Jai
Vishwakarma Bhagwan, Jai Hanuman Ji, have
mercy on me, look at me, kill me as soon as you kill me [laughs]
[music]
Come on, come on, Didi, father-in-law  Maiya, I got the puja done and
asked for more,
okay, let's go
[music]
[music] take the
little one, take it [screaming sound] take the
rest, do
n't make it and die after eating it [music]
take out the bowl, take the rest, if you want then Maiya, we are two people, you
give me one more glass, we both can eat, Maiya,
Kachi had said that in one glass, drink
less food and more water, listen, summer
time is bad, listen, it is only during summer that
I have a full stomach, don't do it like this,
listen, give me the expenses, go and get it prepared quietly, if you talk too
much then it will stop from tomorrow,
you take it,
oh brother, oh
take it [laughter]
Maiya, listen so much, listen if you are not there then I am
Sati,
father
's food,
all the days you get it in
advance, listen, if you
talk too much then stop it from tomorrow
[music]
[laughter]
oh brother, oh oh
[music]
[music] what should I do, sister, what should I do,
plan your murder  Why do
n't we live like this at home, one potato, one
tomato in one oil, how can we spend our life, so give it to
one, sister, cut the potato and tomato,
if you don't worry, cut it the way you want,
grind it and cut it, see [laughs]
no, mother, tell me Kochi, I was just saying that it is so
nice that we get a mother-in-law, in equal proportion,
okay, which one should I get at home
[music]
[music] I want to be so beautiful,
when you look closely, I want to be so beautiful, when you look closely, I want to be so beautiful
[laughs] I want to
show off my beauty, I want to show off my beauty, I want to decorate it, I want to decorate it, I want to decorate it, my sister-in-law
[laughs] hey, you are joking with me, see, I
brother-in-law, I would have hit you with a stick, if you are
joking with me, then
throw you into the father-in-law's stove
[laughs]
father-in-law has this habit that when the wife does
make-up, the father-in-law sits and watches, okay, okay,
sorry, it's done, I did not eat food,
such
food is not ready yet, I am not ready for it.
Sister's brother, you won't be able to make a Khan wherever you go, so
listen, otherwise mother and father, I will take some
land, I am building a house for sister, it does
n't go away every month, one month is all you have to do, son
of Patangiya, Baji, you have to
apply it on your wife's forehead, keep it
on your forehead, if there is no
poison then if
you do black
magic then I will talk, no, not
now,
sister's brother, then do black magic on my son, now I do
n't stop, come along, come along, Baji,
you are
talking about a sister, you are free to beat Baji, it's
okay, let's go
[Music]
Hey Sir, I am talking about Mehrwa, Mehrwa's Sir, I do
n't give you any work,
Namaste Sir, you are well versed,
we are your parents, mother-in-law, mother-in-law, we are very happy,
come on, come on, let the old man keep blabbering
[laughs] I
was blabbering about Dhanshra, come on, when you return, feed
both the Mogis, I will tell you, come and
eat yourself [Music]
take it, get it chopped, get it chopped and get out  From here, the
old earnings started, in Kobara, in Khawara,
everyone here goes to Delhi, Punjab, the old ones get
work, oh did you tell me or not, I
saw you early, as if you were being impudent, laugh, don't you say, it suits me, it's definitely a fallacy,
didi, come on,
tell me, go, or not, go, cut it,
this bad sister, it seems that my Harpan
Durga ji is coming, son, run away
from here, brother,
look, you are thinking, get out
of the house, sit idle, eat, go, go,
see, cut it, catch it [laughs]
now it's fun to teach a lesson to Sasuiya, didi,
yes, Choti, you were right, now see,
how did Sasuiya drank water,
but I have to go, didi, the wind is very hot,
so let's go, let's go,
yes, it's okay, let's go
[music] what is this,
Polwa, on the acre, let's go, let's go [
music] take it, have you
not done it properly
[music] have you done it,
yes, didi, it's been a long time,
decorate your
hands well  If you see this much then
didi, didn't you go and worship it or do it
naked, worship it well, it would not have been this much,
worship it in such a way that you spoil the head of mother-in-law by cutting it in one go,
okay
God, do it well
[Music]
Didi, both of them have come sitting,
both of them have thought that the spade is to be worshipped, yes didi,
worship the spade, didi, don't kill the woman, go and worship it like that,
see how it is worshipped [Music]
[Music]
why is the spade put on the hoe,
why is the spade put on the father-in-law's head,
didi, I will cut the grass, didi, I will cut the
grass, if I start cutting the grass then it is to be worshipped on the wrestler, go and get the
Loharani's spade, I will
see the shopkeeper, didi, do one thing,
you spade,
baba, commit a murder, I will get trapped like this, come,
I will also stop [laughs] wait,
didi, we have gone so close, if we don't cut it then let's
go to Kalta tomorrow
[Music]
come, come, where are you, where are you, tell me,
you tell me quietly
Yes, I will say something, you say it [laughter] and
see what is
in your hands, show me your
hands [screaming] look at
one,
yes, fast in the forest, show both your hands brother, oh oh, look,
something has happened,
you show me your hands,
something is there, look,
you yes, show me, look,
where is something,
show me both your hands,
oh brother, oh,
look, something is
definitely hidden from me, ok, wait, I will
come and see, if you have something in your hand, then if
I say, leave it, I will say something, didi, there is nothing
[music]
no, I have not agreed, both of you are together, first
go, put one forward
[laughter] put
both your hind legs forward,
oh brother, oh,
throw both of you [screaming]
throw it again [laughter]
be fine
[music]
no, both of you, definitely take something secretly,
but check the last look, both of you brothers, ok,
sister, I am such a beautiful wife, why don't you
leave me, if someone else
runs away with firecrackers, then I am so beautiful,
good, if I don't find mine, then I will run away
[laughter] Papa, I should not go out, oh no,
Pranam Bhaiya, stay
happy, friend,
Pranam ji,
stay happy,
where should I go to get Bhaiya's clothes
ironed, I have not ironed them for a long time, I should get them ironed from
there, okay, so let's go to
both of their houses,
iron them later,
okay, let's go, let's
go
[music]
Mother, oh mother,
Didi, Nandi Didi,
we will cut the work for one [laughter]
Pranam Bhaji, stay
happy, stay happy, stay happy, I have brought you
here